btek is the global leader in the
production of organic acids that provide
flavor and function in food production
applications these acids are found in
nature and provide these unique sour
flavors you find them in candies all
sorts of sodas milk-based beverages
baked goods and Industrial applications
as well what we really try to provide is
a high quality product that will appeal
to customers across the globe when I
arrive our production management system
was paper based when you have paper
that's moving around the plant it's not
generating any awareness of how many
pallets and how many bags have been used
we realized we needed something that
could connect disparate systems we
migrated everything into business
Central as really a foundational element
to make solid smart business decisions
prior to Dynamics 365 we really did not
know how long it would be to produce a
palet of product we never really
monitored properly our raw materials now
everything is put into production order
we can see everything made from the
moment it was produced to the time it
was shipped business Central is a
complete system for running our business
without business Central and powerups we
would not be able to keep up with what
our customers desire out of us the
people on the manufacturing side they
don't need to worry about data entry
because everything sinks back to
business Central through power apps
power app transformed our reporting
people are getting data that they didn't
even know really existed before and they
had no way of capturing and they can
trace anything they want through the
entire ecosystem we're a small mensiz
business but the fact that we can
service the entire world is pretty
incredible and it's business Central
that allows us to do that we have a
process now to do everything in our
business workflow we've been able to
condense the amount of time it takes us
to get an order from released to
finished and that has really help to
support our growth and expansion
business Central in the Power Platform
really lets us leverage a small team and
create very big outcomes as we move into
more automated planning and bringing in
AI assisted demand planning I know
Microsoft and business Central are there
the more productive we are the more
competitive we are the better supplier
we can be to our
customers